[Music]
Great morning everyone and hello
deliverers.
Before anything else, let me introduce
myself.  I am La Plo, unit manager of
Tiger Treasure.  And for today's video, I
would love to share with you about the
education insurance of Sunlife education
fund with life insurance and that is Sun
Maxel Prime for your child.  Okay, let's
start.
So what's inside the Sun Maxeling Prime?
Of course, we have life insurance
coverage that is included in this plan,
because it is education insurance.  Our plan automatically
includes life insurance
coverage.  And this plan
is 10 years to pay only and insured
until age 88 years old.  And the life
insurance coverage is times 200%
of the face amount.  So times 2 now.
Whatever the face amount is, times
2 is the life insurance coverage.
All for this plan,
we have a face amount of 350,000.
I'll repeat in my other videos,
I've already explained what
face amount means.  That's it, what the
face amount means is this is
your benefit here in the plan.  This is
the benefit.  This is not what
you will pay in full, but this is
your benefit in this plan.  And the face amount
is equivalent to the life insurance.
That's why I said earlier that
life insurance coverage is 200% of the face amount.
So show so 350
2 automatic life insurance
coverage is,000.
But in this plan, the insured is the
child because this plan is for him
.  The child is the insured until
age 88. So vice versa, if
the plan is for you, you are the insured.  But in this
plan, the child's plan is for him, so
the child is insured until age 88. Is
that clear?  Are
the children clear?
There you go.  And then we have additional
benefit or supplementary benefit.   This
means we have riders.
He is an additional benefit in
our plan.  Aside from the primary
benefits, this is the primary
benefit.  There you go.  This is it.
So we have total disability benefit for
the child.  There is a waiver of premium
.  And then we have accidental debt
dismemberment and disability benefit
of 350,000.
If for example the cost of debt of the
insured is due to accident, Sunlife will
pay an additional 350,000 to the
beneficiaries plus the 700,000.  So
he will be over 1 million.
That's it.  If the
insured's cost of debt is not due to accident, Salif
will pay the life insurance coverage
only plus the fund value and
dismemberment disability benefit.
I'll tell you about that later.  Okay.  And
the last benefit is the waiver of premium
upon death or disability of the initial
owner.  When we say initial owner,
he is also the policy owner.
If, for example, the policy owner is
also an additional life insurance policyholder,
only the policy owner can
withdraw from the child's funds.  There is nothing
else.  Mr. can't.
The neighbor can't.  You are the only one who knows
who the policy owner is.  So is
Baguets' education fund safe?
Okay.  So back to the topic.
If the
policy owner becomes in debt or has a total disability
, and
the 10 years have not been paid yet and that happens, Sunlife
will wave the payment.  Sunlife will
continue the payment and
the child's benefit will continue.  Sunlife will finish
paying.
Okay.  And that's the other benefit
.  Of course,
before there are benefits, there must be payment,
right?
There you go.  So for daddy is 35 years old
and baby boy is zero.  That
newborn is newly born.  Actually, if
the child is 7 days old, you can get it as
early as 7 days old, as long as you have a
birth certificate, baby book,
those are fine, even
just a birth certificate from the
hospital or something, a
baptismal certificate is also fine.  Okay, okay.
That's possible.
Okay.  So back to the topic again.
Our quarterly payment for a 0
year old
male is Php4,685.69.
And if you want annual payment, this is
the annual payment.  That's it.  18,742.77.   Do
you also want it to be semiannual?  That's okay too
.  Just divide it by two.  That's
our quarterly, every 3 months
.
And
upon approval of the plan, when
the plan is approved on day
one, the child is immediately insured
until age 88 years old.  Even up to 88
years old.  Day one is just day one
.
And let's scroll down the other
benefits.
[Music]
There you go.  This is what I was saying earlier
accidental death dismemberment and
disability benefit.  That's it.  I
also put the baby's plan like this
because it was my decision.  Rest.  There you go.
Of course, it's better to just take it,
I'm still confused.
You're just going to get a plan, so make the
most of it because this benefit
is until the child's age 70.
There you go.  So for example,
these are the dismemberment, these are the ones here in the
column.  Accidental deb,
the dismemberment benefit I mentioned earlier,
when one of the things
listed here happens,
for example, hearing of both ears, I'm
deaf, I'm usually deaf, I'm already a little
deaf, I'm not even
70, right, so hearing of both ears, I've
lost my hearing, someone can
get 50% of Php350,000.
This is up to 70, so
that's possible.  site of one eye.  There
really are those and so on.  As long as this is in the
column here in the list, what will
happen is that the insured will receive the
principal, percentage of principal,
and dismemberment benefit and
disabled benefit.
All.  And there you go
.
for everyone's information.  Ah,
there you have it for total disability benefit, this
is up to 60 years old.
accidental
debt dismemberment and disablement
benefit or a D up to age 70
insured and waiver of premium
upon death or disability of policy
owner this is only up to age 21 years
old for children this happens
when for example
baguets was 14 years old when he took out.
So of course, after 10 years, when
the plan ends, he'll be 24 plus.  Once you
turn 21, the premium waiver is no longer available
.  Well, he won't be until age 88
because he's only a rider.
He is just an additional here at our plant.
There you go.  And the exciting part.
You're the one, why are
you saying it's all about insurance? Of course, that's what's
on the first page, so let's
jump to the last page.  Chares, of course,
this is what
we've been waiting for the most.  This is the education
fund.
This is Fue.
There you go.  What is the fund value?  It's simple
.  This is the interest your money earns
annually until the child is 88 years old
.  That's up to 88 because
baby is zero?  0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 to 88.
There you go.  I'll just cut him off
when it's 20 so it won't be too
long so we can see everything here.
There you go.  So does the policy fund have 48
and 10% there?  That's simple,
fund value is allocated to the
stock market.
The stock market, to make it easier to
understand,
is for exchanging
money.  I'm sure you've heard
about the stock market.
The other type of stock market is where
stockholders buy your capital from
other companies here in the Philippines.
The multimillionaire
companies, the ones like Jollibee, Chow King,
PLDT and so on.  You will become a stockholder
in a small amount,
so it will grow.  The rest is in the
government.  There you go.  And this is fan
value.
Your fund value is allocated to the
bond fund.  I put it on the bond fan
because its
growth and shrinkage are only moderate.
His movements, in short.
But he is the one who
returns the best.
Okay.  So the fund's fund value is what is
exchanged for money.  Every second,
every minute, he changes his
value.  So we cannot guarantee the
exact fun value.
As long as he falls here.  That's
4, 8 or 10%.
How does fund value arise?
So this is what he looks like.  For one year, in the
first year of the policy, the
annual payment is Php18,743.
And for the first year company
charge, Php14,430.
Those two will just be minuses.
And that will be the change,
that's it.  That's
Sunlife's purchase of your shares in the stock
market.  and so on as long as
you pay until then.  And I said
earlier that this is what will be
Baguets' educational fan.  There you go.  So
the child is advised to be at least 18 years old to
withdraw.
I'll just draw it, in case I get it wrong, guys
.  There you go.  So at 18 years old, if
you want to withdraw and
the fund value falls by 4%, you
have 194,000.
If 8% you have 324,000
if 10% you have Php416,000.
Any of these three.
This is possible, this is possible,
this is possible.  There,
there he is in brackets.  It can still
increase because it's not from
day one, from the day you take it
, you're always here at 4%.  That's not true
.  As long as he's there, 4, 8
or 10%.
You can monitor him because we have a
website.  You can
register there if
you are already a Sunlife policy holder.  You will see
your fan value there.  And also,
we have a mobile application that
Sunlife can download to our cellphones.
You can also see there how much
your fan value is.
Just be at least 18 years old.  If it's not really
necessary, that's even
better.  As you can see, as time goes on
,
the fund value just keeps getting bigger and bigger.
Okay.  And
wait, I'll erase it again
so our blackboard children don't mess up
.
So we have two options for how you will
use the fan volume.
This is just my advice to
my clients.  Our first option is that
you will take 70% of the fund value.
As long as you get 70% total, until
the plan is completed, you will get 70% of the fund value,
either all at once or
gradually.
[Music]
What's the difference, which one is
better?  Will you take it all at once
or gradually?  There you go.  So let's see.  For
example, does a 20 year old get that?  So
let's say here because it's 8%, right?
Let's remove the odd one.  For example,
this is your winraw.  How much
is left in his plan?  Php 00,000,
right?
Well, your winraw is just a but, right?  Not
the 70%.  So the only thing that will happen
is that that
300,000 will be
rolled over by
Sunlife.  That's what
you'll be turning your capital into in
your fund value.  It's just for business.
You have lost your capital.  Of course,
the capital you have left is all
you'll have to turn over.  So, it would be
better to do it gradually so that
the rotation is still large.
[Music]
And our second option is that you will take 100% of the
fund value.
But take note of that.  If
we had done this second option,
the plan would have been terminated.  Yes,
even if you finish paying,
the plan will be terminated.  As long as
you take all the fund value.
Because
this plan is that
if there is no more funds, even a peso,
it will be terminated.  So
if this is option one
we do,
life insurance will continue.  But if
we do option two,
the plan will be terminated.
The child no longer has insurance.
But it's okay.   It
depends on our needs in
the future.  If, for example,
this is really all you have, is this
your only backup?  It's okay to
take all the fun value.  Don't
regret the insurance because
you took out this plan
to support
your child's education, right?  So it's okay
as long as
you use what
the plan is really for, right?
And later on, when he gets older,
gets a job, he can be the
one to get insurance.  So it depends
on the need.  If it's not really
necessary, that's okay.  Just leave it
there.  That's just a man's man
.
Okay.  That's all.
It's up to you whether you leave it, leave it
or take it all.  It depends, it
depends, it depends on the need.
There you go.  And for the debt benefit,
the debt benefit that I mentioned earlier,
the life insurance coverage is ,000.
Right?
This debt benefit is simple
.
Upon the insured's debt, regardless of
age, how much is left in the
fund value,
including what the 700,000 will get.
So in short, fund plus the
life insurance coverage.
That's a plus.  That's what
the beneficiaries will get.
Of course, if we have
withdrawals from the plan, of course, fewer
withdrawals.
As long as there is enough of the
fan value left, that includes the life
insurance coverage that the
beneficiaries will get.
And that's why I say that this is a legacy for
our children because later on in the
future, the ones who will benefit from their
life insurance coverage are
their future families.
Because let's think, mommies and
daddies, it's even better if
we prepare for the education of
our children.  Because after 20 years,
inflation may be higher, making
education more expensive.  But what's more important is that
you at least have something saved
rather than nothing.
And it is something that will help you.   Is
n't this plan just like a
piggy bank, literally a piggy bank?
You lose money but there is a return,
it has interest annually.   It's
literally like a piggy bank, but
with interest, and your child still has insurance
.  Actually,
we can increase this fund value.
We can add an excess
premium here.  If, for example, you want
the fund value to be higher, you have an
extra budget, we can
add an additional Php2,000.  We will add
that to the excess premium.
We will pay that excess premium to increase the fund
value.  That won't be added to the
life insurance, but the capital will be added
to your fund value
to increase it.
For example, at Christmas,
baby will have money again.  You can also
put excess premium here again.  The
bigger the excess premium, the
better the fun value.
What is special about this plan for your
child?  Of course, aside from being affordable
, you can now save for your child's
education plan.
Give your child something more than just
love, a lifetime of financial security.
Don't forget to like, subscribe and share.
[Music]